{"data":[{"question":"They have been in the reading room since ___.","a":"it had been open","b":"a long time","c":"two hours","d":"eight o'clock","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Since + a particular time or event in the past until the present, or in that period of time","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"60","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"The twin sisters and the twin ___ brothers are all pupils of ___.","a":"the Class Two","b":"Class Second","c":"Second Class","d":"Class Two","answer":"4","explain":"\n- We often say \" class five, chapter two...\"","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"60","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"The association made a ___ brochure.","a":"two-thousand-word","b":"two-thousand-words","c":"two-thousands-words","d":"two-thousands-word","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Compound Adjectives with Numbers: number+ name of thing (in singular) \n- Usually, hyphens are used to link the words together to show that it is one adjective ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"60","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"About ___ of the students in that community college are senior citizens.","a":"three-fourths","b":"two-fourths","c":"three-fourth","d":"three-fours","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Three-fourths = three out of four","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"60","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"The famous poet began to write poems in her ___.","a":"twenty","b":"twentieth","c":"twenties","d":"twenty's","answer":"3","explain":"\n - In her twenties= age from 21-29","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"60","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"When is your birthday? \"It's on Thursday ___.\"","a":"the eleventh of May","b":"eleventh May","c":"the eleven of May","d":"eleven May","answer":"1","explain":"\n- The eleventh of May = 11\/05","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"60","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"By 8:00, ___ members had arrived, after a while ___ got here.","a":"eight, nineth","b":"forty, forty-first","c":"nineteen, a twenty","d":"eleven, a twelfth","answer":"4","explain":"\n - A twelfth= the twelfth person","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"60","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"There will be more than 3 ___ teams taking part in the contest.","a":"hundreds","b":"hundred","c":"hundred of","d":"hundreds of","answer":"2","explain":"\n- One, two, three...+ hundred + noun","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"60","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"___ of the VCDs and DVDs ___ able to be borrowed from the library.","a":"Two-fifth, is","b":"Two-five, is","c":"Two-fifths, is","d":"Two-fifths, are","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Two- fifths= two out of five : plural","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"60","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"A nucleus is about _________ of an atom.","a":"one millionth the size","b":"one million","c":"a million","d":"millions","answer":"1","explain":"- Nucleus: the central part of an atom, consisting of protons and neutrons","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"60","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"}]}